Hello Hello Welcome Friends My name is Kiran
and welcome to this YouTube channel of Straight Solution.
Today in our video we will
talk about a private sector bank
whose name is ICICI Bank. On the
chart of ICICI Bank, we have
seen a very good cricket,
about which we will
discuss you in this video today. So let's
start. As you can see, the
chart of ICICI Bank has opened in front of us
and first of all I would like to
tell you that the chart which is open in front of us is a
weekly chart and if we
look at this chart carefully, we will
see a clear-cut breakdown on it. If we
look at this chart carefully, then
ICICI Bank had made a lifetime high some time back
which was almost a lifetime high of five hundred
rupees and this lifetime
high level has been broken by ICICI Bank in a
very good manner this week, which
means
we have seen a breakdown of the lifetime high level on the chart of ICICI Bank
and not only this, for the
last few weeks
we have seen a lot of breakdown in ICICI Bank.  A strong volume
builder is also being witnessed, which
creates even more conviction within this trend. Now, since ICICI
Bank is trading on a life issue, it's
a little difficult to estimate upcoming targets.
However, we can
activate future targets using fiddling.
As you can see, I've
plotted Fibonacci above.
If we use it to look at future targets, the
first target that appears is the
₹661
level. The second target that appears is the
₹727 level. Meaning, ₹661 and ₹727 are
two targets we could see within ICICI Bank
in the coming time.
So, let's go to the NSC website
and see
what kind of trading we saw within ICICI Bank over NSC in the last trading session,
as you can
see.  The NSC
website has opened in front of us and the
details of ICICI Bank are above in front of us.
If we talk about the last trading session, then it will be
seen above 617,
approximately Rs.11.30 paise below. If we
look at the phone, then
it has closed with a fall of approximately 1.80 cents. If you
look at its price, then we will
see it at Rs.628.30 paise. It opened just
above Rs.628.30 paise. It
makes an oil of 635.35 paise. We
get to see Rs.611 inside it. If
we look below, ICICI Bank has
made a new 52-week high in the last trading session, which is approximately Rs.600.35 paise.
If we put it below, then
its last trading session
's updated situation will open in front of us. If we
talk about the last trading session, the
quantity traded in it is
around Rs.3 crore 20 lakh 15 thousand.  The
deliverable quantity is
around 1 crore 15 lakh 70 thousand
and the percentage
of delivery is around 36.15 70% and the
delivery
loot, so these were some details in front of us
about a village which we have
seen on the chart of ICICI Bank, so
with this I complete my video,
pause this video, SIM is not provided,
before taking any kind of action, do consult your advisor
and do it at the end of your life and if
you liked the video then do
not forget to like and share this video and do
subscribe to our channel, thank you